streetdirectory.com.sg 2015-12-02

# Privacy Policy

****Privacy Policy****

 **1\. General Principles**

This Privacy Policy describes how Streetdirectory Pte Ltd. (“Streetdirectory.com”) collects and uses the personal information you provide on our Web site:  www.Streetdirectory.com. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can Find, Replace, Access and Update this information.

We built Streetdirectory.com, WebPages and Mobile App Management Systems to enable you to create and share web based content with your friends and people around you. We understand you may not want everyone to have access to your hosted at Streetdirectory.com; that is why we give you control of your personal content.

Streetdirectory.com helps you share content with others. You choose what content you make available to the general users of  Streetdirectory.com

Streetdirectory.com is based on the accumulation of user provided and/or formed content and there is an increasing amount of content being made available for Streetdirectory.com users. Streetdirectory.com sees it as its goal to help its users have as much content as possible available for their use while retaining each users privacy.

**2\. Acceptance**

By using or accessing Streetdirectory.com, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

This Privacy policy covers any and all actions on the www.Streetdirectory.com website (the "Website").

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact our privacy staff at privacy@Streetdirectory.com.

**3\. Collection and Providence of Information and Content**

When you visit Streetdirectory.com you provide us with two types of information: limited personal information and content you knowingly choose to disclose and/or post on the Streetdirectory.com website

When you register with Streetdirectory.com, you provide us with certain personal information, such as your email address. When you enter Streetdirectory.com, we use third party utility-tracking partners to collect your browser type and IP address through log files. This information is gathered for all Streetdirectory.com visitors. In addition, we store certain information from your browser using "cookies." A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. We do link the information we store in cookies to any personal information you submit while on our website. By default, we use a persistent cookie that stores your login ID and password to make it easier for you to login when you come back to Streetdirectory.com. You can remove or block this cookie using the settings in your browser if you want to disable this convenience feature.

The use of cookies by our tracking utility company is not covered by our privacy statement. We do not have access or control over these cookies.

You post User Content (as defined in the Streetdirectory.com Terms of Use) on the Site at your own risk. We cannot control the actions of other Users with whom you may choose to share your pages and content. Therefore, we cannot and do not guarantee that User Content you post on the Site will not be viewed (or even harmed) by unauthorized persons. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Site. You understand and acknowledge that, even after removal, copies of User Content may remain viewable in cached and archived pages or if other Users have copied or stored your User Content.

**4\. Billing information**

Should you sign up for a Paid Services (as defined in the Terms of Use), we will require your billing information along with information such as your name, phone number and address in order to process the transaction and to collect the fees involved.

We do not store your billing information, and this information will be discarded after your transaction has been processed. Nevertheless, the required information for your billing will be stored by our payment gateway company which will store your billing information on their secure payment gateway for as long as necessary to carry out the terms of your subscription.

We may retain the last 4 digits of your credit card number, and credit card type, so that you may identify the card used in the future.

Should you cancel your subscription, your billing information will be removed by the payment gateway company.

**5\. Sharing Your Content with Third Parties**

We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy statement. We do not sell your personal information to third parties. 

We may provide information and/or personal user content to service providers to help us provide the services we offer. Specifically, we may use third parties to facilitate our business, such as to host the service at a co-location facility for servers, to provide you with our community blog, to send out email updates about Streetdirectory.com, to remove repetitive information from our user lists, to process payments for products or services and to provide you with our live chat services. In connection with these business operations, our service providers may have access to your personal information and/or content for use for a limited time in connection with these business activities. When you sign up for our services, we will share your personal information only as necessary for the third party to provide that service.  

We occasionally provide demonstrations of user created content that allow non-users a glimpse into the Streetdirectory.com world. Such content is provided in a form which protects your content from any unauthorized editing and/or changing. We may be required to disclose your personal information pursuant to lawful requests, such as subpoenas or court orders, or in compliance with applicable laws. We do not reveal information until we have a good faith belief that an information request by law enforcement or private litigants meets applicable legal standards. Additionally, we may share account or other information when we believe it is necessary to comply with law, to protect our interests or property, to prevent fraud or other illegal activity perpetrated through the Streetdirectory.com service or using the Streetdirectory.com name, or to prevent imminent bodily harm. This may include sharing information with other companies, lawyers, agents or government agencies.

We may offer or provide services jointly with other companies on Streetdirectory.com such as when you purchase your domain name through our Website. In such case we shall provide clear disclosure of such third party's in the providence of such service on Streetdirectory.com, and in such case we shall be entitled to share customer information such as user ID with such third party in connection with your use of such joint services. In any case in which the ownership of Streetdirectory.com's business shall change, your user information may be transferred to the new owner so the service can continue operations. You will be notified via email and/or prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information.

When you use Streetdirectory.com, certain information you post or share with third parties (e.g., a friend or someone in your network), such as personal information, comments, messages, photos, videos or other information, may be shared with other users. All such sharing of information is done at your own risk.

**6\. Communications from the Website**

We will use your email address in order to send you promotional emails. If you no longer wish to receive these emails you may follow the unsubscribe instructions contained in the promotional communications which you receive.

**7\. Links**

Streetdirectory.com may contain links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other web sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personal information. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by Streetdirectory.com or posted on the Streetdirectory.com website.

**8\. Public Forums**

Our Website offers publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, contact us at: privacy@Streetdirectory.com. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

**9\. Social Media Widgets**

Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Streetdirectory “Save” [and Widgets, such as the “Connect with Facebook” or interactive mini-programs that run on our site]. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

**10\. Changing or Removing Content**

Access and control over personal content on Streetdirectory.com is possible through the content editing tools. Streetdirectory.com users may modify or delete any of their personal content at any time by logging into their account. Any such changes will be updated immediately. Users who wish to deactivate their Streetdirectory.com account may do so on the My Account page. Removed information may persist in backup copies for a reasonable period of time but will not be generally available to users of Streetdirectory.com.

If your personal information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, delete/deactivate it by emailing our Customer Support at cs@Streetdirectory.com. We will respond to your request to access within 30 days.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

**11\. Security**

Streetdirectory.com takes appropriate precautions to protect our users' information and content. We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards which protect your account information and uploaded content. Because email and instant messaging are not recognized as secure communications, we request that you not send private information or data to us by email or instant messaging services. If you have any questions regarding the security of Streetdirectory.com Website, please contact us at privacy@Streetdirectory.com.

**12\. Testimonials**

We post customer testimonials on our web site which may contain personally identifiable information.  We do obtain the customer's consent via email prior to posting the testimonial to post their name along with their testimonial. If you wish to request the removal of your testimonial you may contact us at cs@Streetdirectory.com.

**13\. Contests**

From time-to-time we may provide you the opportunity to participate in contests or on our Website. If you participate, we will request certain personal information from you. Participation in these contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as postal code).

We use this information to notify contest winners and award prizes, to monitor site traffic and to provide notices

to participants.

Streetdirectory may use third party service providers to conduct surveys or contests. We will not share the personal information you provide through a contest or survey with other third parties unless we give you prior notice and choice.

**14\. Terms of Use, Notices and Revisions**

Your use of Streetdirectory.com, and any disputes arising from it, is subject to this Privacy Policy as well as our General Terms of Use and all of its general provisions including warranty disclaimer, limitation of liability, indemnity and choice of law. We may update this privacy statement to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Website prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices. Unless stated otherwise, our current privacy policy applies to all information that we have about you and to any of your account.

**15\. Contacting Streetdirectory Pte Ltd**

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please contact us at privacy@Streetdirectory.com. You may also contact us by mail at: 305 Alexandra Road, #05-12 Vantage Automotive Centre, Singapore 159942. Tel: +65 6474 4005
